A Guide to the Governor's Office, Executive Mansion Director, Records, 1973-1995
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Office of the Governor, Executive Mansion Director, Records, 1973-1995
Library of Virginia
36470
9 cubic feet.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access to architectural and engineering plans and drawings of current governmental buildings requires a written request from the prospective user and written authorization from the appropriate authority within the agency occupying the facility.
Acquisition Information
Transferred from the Office of the Governor, Executive Mansion, on 5 May 1999.
Biographical/Historical Information
During the colonial period of Virginia's history the governor, as an appointee of the Crown, was the colony's principal representative and upholder of royal authority. Although his powers were limited somewhat by the Council and by the laws passed by the House of Burgesses, the governor still had the authority to prorogue, adjourn, or dissolve the legislature, to confirm or veto its acts, to preside as the chief jurist of the colony, to command the provincial military forces, and to appoint many of the subordinate officers of government.
Most of these powers, excepting the military and appointive, were swept away by the American Revolution. The several revolutionary conventions assumed the executive role in 1774 and 1775 until the Committee of Safety was created in July 1775 to function in that capacity. The constitution adopted in 1776 made the governor subordinate to the legislative branch, elected by the General Assembly and circumscribed by a Council of State appointed by the assembly.
It was not until the constitution of 1851 was adopted that the power of the governor was strengthened appreciably. The Council of State was abolished, and the governor was popularly elected. In subsequent years his authority was consolidated and expanded to statute, and his veto power was restored. The state government reorganization act passed by the General Assembly on April 18, 1927, firmly established the governor as the chief administrative officer of a government composed of departments, the directors of which serve at the pleasure of the governor. In addition, the organization of the governor's staff has increased in size and complexity until it has become virtually a department itself: the Office of the Governor, encompassing both the chief executive and his staff.
Scope and Content Information
Contains documentation of the work of the Executive Mansion director, including records of events and renovations. Also included are materials related to the Citizens' Advisory Council on Furnishing and Intepreting the Executive Mansion, the celebration of the 175th Anniversary of the Executive Mansion. Materials include correspondence, photographs, decorative samples, and architectural drawings.
Organized into ten (10) series: I. Event files; II. DGS/Special Projects Files; III. Historic Attractions/Associations/Tours Files; IV. General Mansion Information, etc.; V. Citizens' Advisory Council on Furnishing and Intepreting the Executive Mansion Files; VI. 175th Anniversary of the Executive Mansion Files; VII. Miscellaneous; VIII. Architectural Drawings, Renderings and Other Plans; IX: Photographs, Slides and Negatives; and X. Ephemera.
Series I. Event Files, 1982-1995 is arranged into five (5) subseries and contains memos and notes concerning the preparations and arrangements for events at the Executive Mansion. Included are lists of invitees and guests, menus, sample invitations and menu cards, and notes to the mansion staff. Also included are a transcript of a gathering of former first ladies of Virginia on March 24, 1982, and files for the Southern Governor's Association / African Trade Summit meeting in 1993. Other collections at the Library of Virginia contain event files from the Wilder and Allen administration. Please consult the library catalog for references to these collections.
Series II: DGS/Special Projects Files, 1981-1995 is arranged alphabetically by folder title and contains correspondence, memos and other materials related to the special projects at the Mansion and relations with the Department of General Services. Of particular interest are materials relating to the renovations and improvement projects at the Mansion, including samples of materials used in the renovation and improvement projects. Also contains folders relating to the use of the Mansion by film crews for movies.
Series III: Historic Attractions / Associations / Tourism, 1984-1994 is arranged alphabetically by folder title and contains correspondence, memos and other materials relating to Historic Attractions throughout the Richmond Area and the United States, as well as information on tours given at the Mansion.
Series IV: General Mansion Information, etc. is arranged alphabetically by folder title. Contains correspondence, memos, brochures, and other materials relating to the Executive Mansion. Included in the series is information on specific aspects of the Mansion and its grounds.
Series V: Citizens' Advisory Council on Furnishing and Interpreting the Executive Mansion, 1973-1989 is arranged into three (3) subseries; Contributions; Correspondence; and Financial Information. The Contributions Files, 1973-1990, are arranged chronologically, and contain information regarding monetary and property donations made to the Citizens' Advisory Council on Furnishing and Interpreting the Executive Mansion for the calendar years 1973 through 1990. The Correspondence Files, 1973-1989, are arranged chronologically by date and contain correspondence and other materials relating to the Citizens' Advisory Council on Furnishing and Interpreting the Executive Mansion (formerly the Citizens' Advisory Committee on Furnishing and Interpreting the Executive Mansion). Included in these materials is correspondence regarding the donation and restoration of property for the furnishing of the Mansion as well as correspondence with members of the Citizens' Advisory Council. The Financial Files, 1973-1989, are arranged chronologically and contain information regarding donations to and purchases made by the Citizens' Advisory Council on Furnishing and Interpreting the Executive Mansion from 1973 until 1989. Members of the Citizens' Advisory Council on Furnishing and Interpreting the Executive Mansion transferred these files to the Office of the Director of the Executive Mansion in 1987. These materials compliment the materials found in the Library of Virginia accession 35652 from the Citizens' Advisory Council on Furnishing and Interpreting the Executive Mansion.
Series VI: 175th Anniversary of the Executive Mansion, 1987-1989 is arranged into two (2) subseries: Correspondence and Other Materials, 1987-1989; and Financial Files, 1987-1989. Contains correspondence and financial information relating to the events surrounding the 175th Anniversary of the Executive Mansion. The Citizens' Advisory Council on Furnishing and Interpreting the Executive Mansion (formerly the Citizens' Advisory Committee on Furnishing and Interpreting the Executive Mansion) was responsible for the developing of activities and events for the celebration. Members of the Citizens' Advisory Council on Furnishing and Interpreting the Executive Mansion transferred these files to the Office of the Director of the Executive Mansion in 1987.
Series VII: Miscellaneous, is arranged alphabetically by folder title. Contains correspondence, memos and other items not directly related to the Executive Mansion and its functions.
Series VIII: Architectural Drawings, Renderings and other plans is arranged chronologically and contains architectural drawings related to renovations of the mansion, landscaping plans, window treatments and other decorative points within the Mansion. Some items were removed from folders in other series -- notations of such actions accompany the item and are indicated in the folder listing for each series.
Series IX: Photographs, slides and negatives is arranged into seven (7) subseries and contains photographs, slides and negatives depicting the Mansion, its occupants and events at the Mansion. Many of the photographs were previously used in brochures and other publications about the Executive Mansion, including William Seale's Virginia's Executive Mansion (1988). Photographs are from various sources including the Richmond Newspapers, the Valentine Museum, the Library of Virginia, and from private collections.
Series X: Ephemera is arranged alphabetically by item title. Contains artifacts, videotapes, decorator samples and one book.
Arrangement
Arrangement
Series are arranged alphabetically or chronologically, see series description for specific arrangement information.
Organization
Organized into ten (10) series: I. Event files; II. DGS/Special Projects Files; III. Historic Attractions/Associations/Tours Files; IV. General Mansion Information, etc.; V. Citizens' Advisory Council on Furnishing and Intepreting the Executive Mansion Files; VI. 175th Anniversary of the Executive Mansion Files; VII. Miscellaneous; VIII. Architectural Drawings, Renderings and Other Plans; IX: Photographs, Slides and Negatives; and X. Ephemera.
Contents List
- Event Files 1982, 1986 (Box 1-3)
  Arranged into five (5) subseries. Contains memos and notes concerning the preparations and arrangements for events at the Executive Mansion. Included are lists of invitees and guests, menus, sample invitations and menu cards, and notes to the mansion staff. Please note that the Event Files from the Robb Administration appear to be complete, the files from other administrations are not complete. Other collections at the Library of Virginia contain event files from the Wilder and Allen administration. Please consult the library catalog for references to these collections.
  Chronological and Alphabetical
  - Robb Administration 1982-1986 (Box 1-2)
    Arranged chronologically by date. Contains correspondence, memos and notes concerning the preparations and arrangements made for events at the Executive Mansion during the Robb Administration (1982-1986). This series also includes guest lists and menus for many of the events. Of particular interest is a transcript of a gathering of former first ladies of Virginia on March 24, 1982. This series only includes documentation on official events. Events from family occasions were moved to Subseries I.E: Events spanning multiple administrations, or outside of gubernatorial functions, 1982-1991.
    Chronological
    - Tours 1982 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - General Assembly Receptions 1982 Jan 27-28 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - General Assembly Spouses' Receptions 1982 Jan 27-28 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - "Smokers" Receptions 1982 Feb 9-11, 16-17 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Darden, Colgate - Luncheon 1982 Feb 15 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Page's Activity 1982 Feb 25 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Appreciation Dinner 1982 Mar 2 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - General Assembly & Spouses Informal Party 1982 Mar 12 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - First Ladies' Luncheon 1982 Mar 24 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - First Ladies' Luncheon (photographs) 1982 Mar 24 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Open House - Garden Week 1982 Apr 28-29 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Garden Week 1982 Apr 27-May 1 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Federation of Democratic Women's Clubs Coffee 1982 May 7 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Contributors' Parties 1982 May 14-16 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - First Families Party 1982 May 16 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Economic Development Council Dinner 1982 May 19 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Richmond Ladies Luncheon 1982 May 19 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Retirement Reception for Mr. John Wessells 1982 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Davis Dinner 1982 July 1 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Beach Party for the 1981 Campaign Staff 1982 July 3 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Barone Firm Dinner 1982 July 17 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Cocktail Reception 1982 July 1982 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Violin Recital by Pavel Pakarsky and Reception 1982 Sept 9 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Luncheon for Ministers 1982 Sept 27 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Virginia Laureates Buffet 1982 Sept 28 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Virginia Laureates Buffet 1982 Sept 28 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - University of Virginia Law Alumni Reception 1982 Oct 4 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Hostess Orientation 1982 Oct 13 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Cabinet Diner 1982 Nov 4 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Recognition of Mansion Work Crews 1982 Nov 5 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Commission to Study Future of Virginia Luncheon 1982 Nov 11 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - March of Dimes Tea 1982 Nov 16 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Cocktail Buffet in Honor of Walter P. Chrysler 1982 Dec 2 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Family Open House for Agency Heads, Governor's Staff, and Other 1982 Dec 12 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Christmas Party 1982 Dec 16 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Cabinet Retreat 1982 Dec 15 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Christmas 1982 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Mansion Christmas Decorations 1982 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - General Assembly Entertaining 1983 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Legislative Session 1983 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Sons of the American Revolution Reception 1983 Jan 4 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Congressional Delegate Luncheon 1983 Jan 11 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - New Delegates' Breakfasts 1983 Jan 13-14 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - General Assembly Reception 1983 Jan 13 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Reception - Legislative Support Staff 1983 Jan 17 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - RIF Tea and Luncheon 1983 Jan 26 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Dinner 1983 Jan 27 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Science and Technology Task Force Luncheon 1983 Feb 1 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Legislative Aides Reception 1983 Feb 8 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Pages Event 1983 Feb 10 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Legislative Spouses Coffee 1983 Feb 10 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Senator and Mrs. Willey's Dinner 1983 Feb 18 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - General Assembly Reception 1983 Feb 18 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Democratic Women Officials Reception 1983 Mar 12 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Easter Egg Hunt 1983 Mar 27 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Miles Carpenter Reception 1983 Mar 30 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Candidates' Cocktail Party 1983 Mar 31 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Luncheon - Higher Education Task Force 1983 Mar 31 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Reception for Agency Heads 1983 Mar 31 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Governor's Luncheon after Hardy Memorial Award 1983 Apr 26 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Dinner for Former Governors and Spouses 1983 Apr 26 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Garden Club of Virginia Coffee 1983 Apr 27 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Luncheon - Board of Directors, Virginia Center for the Performing Arts 1983 May 6 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Friends of the Mansion Reception 1983 May 11 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Carol Channing Luncheon 1983 May 12 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Reception for Lobbyists 1983 May 18 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Virginia Women's Cultural History Projects Luncheon 1983 May 23 (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - State Board of Education Luncheon 1983 May 27 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Governor's Staff Cook-out 1983 May 28 (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Governor's Fellows for 1983 Coffee 1983 May 31 (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Luncheon honoring Mrs. Charles Beatty Moore 1983 June 15 (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Coffee - Virginia Community College System Board 1983 June 29 (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Editors' Luncheons 1983 July-Aug (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Ice Cream Social 1983 July 10 (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Governor's Task Force on Science and Technology Luncheon 1983 July 14 (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Reception for Andy Spaulding and Maggie Maupin 1983 July 26 (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - A.E. Dick Howard's Party for Governor's Fellows 1983 July 26 (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - Governor's Task Force on Drunk Driving Reception 1983 July 27 (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - Association for the Preservation of Virginia Antiquities, The Virginia Company Reception 1983 Sept 17 (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - Reception - Kick-off for Job Training Partnership Act Programs in Virginia 1983 Sept 19 (Box 1, Folder 77)
    - Cabinet Forum 1983 Sept 29 (Box 1, Folder 78)
    - Coffee in honor of Minority Business Week - cancelled 1983 Sept 30 (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - Economic Advisory Council Luncheon 1983 Oct 19 (Box 1, Folder 80)
    - Luncheon in Honor of Lt. Col. Guion Bluford 1983 Oct 20 (Box 1, Folder 81)
    - Industrial Development Dinner 1983 Oct 20 (Box 1, Folder 82)
    - Hostess Orientation 1983 Oct 21 (Box 1, Folder 83)
    - Erma Bombeck Dinner 1983 Oct 21 (Box 1, Folder 84)
    - Luncheon for Mr. & Mrs. Mortimer Adler and Mrs. Leslie Cheek 1983 Oct 24 (Box 1, Folder 85)
    - Reception for Azie Taylor Morton 1983 Oct 28 (Box 1, Folder 86)
    - Roadside Beautification Luncheon 1983 Oct 31 (Box 1, Folder 87)
    - Tea in Honor of Mrs. Mary Moody Northen 1983 Nov 9 (Box 1, Folder 88)
    - Cabinet Forum Luncheon 1983 Nov 9 (Box 1, Folder 89)
    - College Presidents' Dinner 1983 Nov 10 (Box 1, Folder 90)
    - Reception / Coffee Re: Dedication of Darden Memorial Garden 1983 Nov 11 (Box 1, Folder 91)
    - Reception - State Party Staff, Governor's Office State, Democratic Leadership 1983 Nov 17 (Box 1, Folder 92)
    - Fairchild Industries Luncheon 1983 Nov 23 (Box 1, Folder 93)
    - Division of Industrial Development Luncheon 1983 Nov 28 (Box 1, Folder 94)
    - Reading Month Kick-Off Coffee 1983 Dec 1 (Box 1, Folder 95)
    - Luncheon 1983 Dec 2 (Box 1, Folder 96)
    - 25th Anniversary Party - Richmond Area Democratic Women 1983 Dec 4 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Open House for State Agency Heads 1983 Dec 12 (Box 1, Folder 97)
    - Mrs. Robb's Christmas Party 1983 Dec 14 (Box 1, Folder 98)
    - Staff Christmas Party 1983 Dec 15 (Box 1, Folder 99)
    - Mansion Christmas Decorations 1983 (Box 1, Folder 100)
    - General Assembly Entertaining 1984 (Box 1, Folder 101)
    - March of Dimes Coffee 1984 Jan 5 (Box 1, Folder 102)
    - Glenn Committee Luncheon 1984 Jan 5 (Box 1, Folder 103)
    - VWCHP Luncheon 1984 Jan 6 (Box 1, Folder 104)
    - Congressional Delegate Luncheon 1984 Jan 10 (Box 1, Folder 105)
    - Leadership Wives - Legislature Opening Session 1984 Jan 11 (Box 1, Folder 106)
    - New Democratic Legislators Breakfast 1984 Jan 12 (Box 1, Folder 107)
    - New Republican Legislators Breakfast 1984 Jan 13 (Box 1, Folder 108)
    - General Assembly Reception 1984 Jan 16-17 (Box 1, Folder 109)
    - Dinner 1984 Jan 19 (Box 1, Folder 110)
    - Menus 1984 Jan 19-May 5 (Box 1, Folder 111)
    - Dinner 1984 Jan 23 (Box 1, Folder 112)
    - Coffee 1984 Jan 26 (Box 1, Folder 113)
    - Tea 1984 Jan 26 (Box 1, Folder 114)
    - Fund Raiser - Al Smith 1984 Jan 26 (Box 1, Folder 115)
    - Dinner 1984 Jan 31 (Box 1, Folder 116)
    - Annie Glenn Coffee 1984 Feb 1 (Box 1, Folder 117)
    - Dinner 1984 Feb 1 (Box 1, Folder 118)
    - Legislative Dinner 1984 Feb 2 (Box 1, Folder 119)
    - Legislative Dinner 1984 Feb 6 (Box 1, Folder 120)
    - Legislative Dinner 1984 Feb 9 (Box 1, Folder 121)
    - Dinner 1984 Feb 13 (Box 1, Folder 122)
    - Dinner 1984 Feb 14 (Box 1, Folder 123)
    - Reception for Legislative Support Staff 1984 Feb 15 (Box 1, Folder 124)
    - Reception - Legislative Support Staff 1984 Feb 20 (Box 1, Folder 125)
    - Reception for Pages and Page Staff 1984 Feb 23 (Box 1, Folder 126)
    - Press Reception 1984 Mar 8 (Box 1, Folder 127)
    - End-of-the-Session Sing-Along 1984 Mar 9 (Box 1, Folder 128)
    - Cabinet Dinner 1984 Mar 19 (Box 1, Folder 129)
    - Mansion Tours Co-Hostesses Coffee 1984 Mar 20 (Box 1, Folder 130)
    - Wine and Cheese Reception, Leadership Metro Richmond 1984 Apr 4 (Box 1, Folder 131)
    - Public Relations Society of America, Old Dominion Chapter, Award Presentation 1984 Apr 13 (Box 1, Folder 132)
    - Luncheon for Debbie Wood and Richard Dickerson 1984 Apr 16 (Box 1, Folder 133)
    - North-South Summit Breakfast [Southern Governors' Association] 1984 Apr 27 (Box 1, Folder 134)
    - Mary Matthews Reception 1984 May 6 (Box 1, Folder 135)
    - Henry Howell Reception 1984 May 7 (Box 1, Folder 136)
    - Henry Howell Reception 1984 May 17 (Box 1, Folder 137)
    - Governor's Arts Awards 1984 May 18 (Box 1, Folder 138)
    - Fellows of the Virginia Museum Dinner 1984 May 18 (Box 1, Folder 139)
    - Candidate Development Reception 1984 May 31 (Box 1, Folder 140)
    - Cabinet Forum Luncheon 1984 June 1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Governor's Fellows Coffee 1984 June 4 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Passport Tour Dinner 1984 June 6 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Mansion Committee Meeting and Reception 1984 June 7 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Wayne Anderson Luncheon 1984 June 28 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Beach Party at Camp Pendleton for Governor's Staff, Fellows, Cabinet and Deputies 1984 July 7 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Southern Governors' Association, Virginia Business Council Opening Reception 1984 July 8 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Division of Industrial Development Luncheon 1984 July 13 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Governor's Fellows Piano Recital and Dessert Soiree 1984 July 24 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Luncheon for Dr. Timothy Sullivan 1984 Aug 9 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Olympic Ceremony and Reception 1984 Sept 18 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Arts Awards Luncheon 1984 Sept 26 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Division of Industrial Development Luncheon 1984 Sept 27 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Baby Shower Honoring Pearl Walden Thomas 1984 Oct 3 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Baby Shower Honoring Pearl Walden Thomas 1984 Nov 1 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Dessert Soiree for Notable Living Women 1984 Nov 30 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - December Open House 1984 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Future's Commission Luncheon 1984 Dec 4 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Department of Economic Development Dinner 1984 Dec 13 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Mansion Christmas Decorations 1984 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Tree Lighting Reception 1984 Dec 14 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Coffee [for volunteers] 1984 Dec 18 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Staff Christmas Party 1984 Dec 20 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Williamsburg Trip 1984 Dec 26-28 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Contributors' Party 1984 Dec 28 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - General Assembly Entertaining 1985 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Apple Blossom Festival 1985 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - State-Festival Forum Luncheon 1985 Jan 7 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Reception following State of the Commonwealth Address 1985 Jan 9 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - March of Dimes Coffee 1985 Jan 10 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Supreme Court Dinner 1985 Jan 14 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Tea for General Assembly Spouses 1985 Jan 22 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Coffee Honoring University of Virginia President Robert O'Neil 1985 Jan 25 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Reception - Governor Clinton 1985 Feb 2 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Southeastern Universities Research Association (SURA) Dinner 1985 Feb 11 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Legislative Staff Reception 1985 Feb 13 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Cocktail Party of Pages 1985 Feb 20 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Sing-Along 1985 Feb 22 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Southeast Compact Commission 1985 Feb 27 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Division of Economic Development Dinner 1985 Mar 6 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Luncheon Honoring Judy Johnson and Pearl Thomas 1985 Mar 15 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Members of the General Assembly Dinner 1985 Mar 18 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Economic Development Luncheon 1985 Mar 19 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Leadership Metro Richmond Reception 1985 Apr 3 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Delegate Selection Reception 1985 Apr 18 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - American Society for Public Administration 1985 May 2 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Arts Awards Reception 1985 May 7 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - State Agency Auxiliary Tea 1985 May 9 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Children's Celebration of the Arts, Capitol Square 1985 May 11 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Governor's Arts Awards Reception 1985 May 18 (Box 2, Folder 50)